<smartdoc name="Facts" id="facts"  title="Interesting Facts and Trivia">
	<smarttab title="Interesting Facts" icon="icons/docs/4.png">
	 <node title="Technology" icon="icons/docs/16.png">
		<node title="Invention Of Zero" icon="icons/docs/11.png">
			<data><![CDATA[
			Zero was invented in India by Indian mathematicians dating as early as 5th century. 
			They widely used it in calculations, astronomy and astrology. Zero was spread by Arabians 
			to the Europe and there on it was spread all over. Before this, all Europeans used roman 
			numerical which were difficult to calculate on as they were in the form of Symbols, 
			lengthy and had limits.
			]]></data>
		</node>
		<node title="Printers Spy On You" icon="icons/docs/23.png">
			<data><![CDATA[
			Printer manufacturers print invisible yellow dots on consumer's prints that check to 
			see if a person is printing counterfeit money. If you call your printer manufacturer and
			 ask them to "please stop spying on you", they will send secret services to your address 
			 to find out why you care about your privacy. Upset? You should be. The more people who 
			 call their printer's manufacturers and make this request, the more likely secret services will refuse to investigate.
			]]></data>
		</node>
	  </node>
	  <node title="Sports" icon="icons/docs/10.png">
	  <node title="Farting Contest" icon="icons/docs/33.png">
			<data><![CDATA[
			In ancient Japan, public contests were held to see who in a town could 
			fart the loudest and longest. Winners were awarded many prizes and received great recognition.
			]]></data>
		</node>
	<node title="Golf Ladies" icon="icons/docs/31.png">
			<data><![CDATA[
			It is the internet myth that the name of the popular Scottish game Golf stands 
			for "Gentlemen Only, Ladies Forbidden." The word golf originates form medieval 
			Scottish and Dutch dialects. Back in a day before the creation of dictionaries,
			 there was no standardized spelling of any given word. So it is believed that 
			 word golf originates from Dutch word "kolf" or "kolve" which meant "club."
			 Later on old Scots dialect transformed the word into "gouf" or "golve ."
			]]></data>
		</node>
	  </node>
	</smarttab>
	<smarttab title="About">
	<data><![CDATA[
				<h4>Interesting Facts by Sheel Khanna</h4>
			]]></data>
	</smarttab>
				
</smartdoc>
